Hey, guys!
We might not take down this boss.
But the next one?
I promise.
That one's ours!
Sorry, guys.
Stand down.
You're not getting past me.
Kirito!
You sure you wanna do this, buddy?
It's a bad idea.
I doubt even you can take
on a whore this big solo.
Yeah, maybe.
There's only one way to find out for sure.
It's your funeral.
Okay, people, you're the man.
Mages, let him have it.
Watch out, Cait!
Cait, steal!
Cait!
The world is more UFC.
No, it's not like the bad mental
world, but not just as a head.
I was still in the light of the past.
I was not even in the past.
I've reached the top of my heart.
Oh give it for my way
No way.
He cut through spells.
That's impossible.
I didn't know he could do stuff like that.
Now you know.
How'd you do that?
Easy.
Compared to a bullet from
a high-powered rifle,
knocking down high-speed
spells is nothing.
Oh, crap.
Battle formation on the double!
I can only hold them for a couple!
Head for the boss room! Hurry!
Oh yeah?
Hold your ground!
There's only one of him!
Not even!
I'm here too!
You can't see me yet! You're late!
What the hell took you so long?
Sorry, man!
Took a wrong turn!
Mine's here too?
Thank you, Yui.
You too, Klein.
And Kirito, I love you.
My friends will take
care of those players.
But if we want to get
into the boss room today,
we'll have to get through the
ones blocking it ourselves.
Gotcha!
Ready?
Yep!
Huh?
Hey!
Hey, no fair!
Think you can heal them
on your own for a bit?
Sure, I should have enough Main for that.
Great, then I'm gonna take
care of those enemy mages.
Yuki! Watch out!
It's the Berserk Healer!
All right, guys, the hard part's next.
Come on, let's get that boss. Right!
Yeah, we will beat him.
Okay, drink your potions, guys.
Max out your HP and MP.
Stick to the plan and we'll have a shot.
We know at the start its
attack patterns are simple.
Stay calm and avoid them.
Asuna.
Those guys.
Those friends of yours.
Aren't they here just to help us?
Yes.
They know it's important to you.
So let's pull this raid off
and make it worth their effort.
Yeah, but...
I mean, we can't let you do all this
and not give you anything in return.
But you have.
You taught me something I'm
always going to remember.
Sometimes you have to fight to
get your point across, right?
Well, this is our last chance at this.
Time's running out.
It won't be long before that guild regroups
and comes charging through that door.
Let's do our best to win, so we can
flash them a victory sign when they do.
Hey, Yuki.
When this battle is over, I want
you to tell me all about yourself.
I want to know about all
the worlds you've been to,
and all the adventures you've had.
Here comes the boss, guys!
Let's mess him up! Right!
Oh, my God.
Say, I feel it!
Only three left.
You guys!
We're almost there!
Don't let up on him!
Great!
That boss sure knows how to defend itself.
You think that's a random move?
Using his arms to block?
Siune, I have an idea
and I need your help.
Can you take over healing for 30 seconds?
Yes, that shouldn't be a problem.
I have enough reserves to cover everyone.
I knew it, that wasn't random, it's protecting
a critical weak spot with that move.
You see that jewel on its chest?
That's where we need to focus our attack.
So we just shatter that
jewel and we can defeat it?
At the very least, we'll
put a dent in its HP.
The thing is, it's too high up to
reach and we can't fly in this dungeon.
Then we'll just use our sword skills
and keep an eye out for counter moves.
Sounds good.
I'll go up front and tell them the plan.
Heal them for a little longer, okay?
Don't worry, I'm on it.
Yuki!
Ashina!
What's going on? Guess what?
I found a weak spot on the boss.
You see that jewel on its chest?
Below the necks?
If you hit that, you'll
do some major damage.
You sure?
Here you go!
It's high!
I couldn't reach it even if I jumped!
You could if you had the
right springboard, though.
Huh?
Tenchi!
When he swings that
hammer again, take a knee!
It's our chance to win.
Good luck, Yugi!
Leave it to me, sis!
Uh... Sis?
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
We did it.
You see that?
We beat him, Asuna.
That we did.
I'm so tired.
We did it.
Yeah, but I'm wiped.
Oh my god
You you you gotta be kidding me?
Great job, you guys.
I'm kind of sad it's over.
Oh, it's not over yet.
There's one last thing to do.
You know, a party.
Oh, of course.
Let's have a big one.
We'll pull out all the stops. Sweet.
We got enough now to
party in style, right?
Mm-hmm.
Where are we going to have it?
Hey, we should go to some big city and
buy out a restaurant for the night.
Um, actually, if you guys want to,
we could have it at my place in-game.
It's small, but cozy. Really?
Yuki, is something wrong?
Um, please forgive us, Asuna.
We really appreciate your
offer to host the party.
It's just that...
Oh, never mind. It's nothing.
We'd be honored to have our
victory party at your home, Asuna.
That settles it.
Guys, we're heading over to
the Lombard Central Market.
We got ourselves some shopping to do.
Let's get some of that ale!
Wow!
Your place is so cool, Asuna!
Wait, there's already food and drinks out!
Now that's what I'm talking about!
I can't wait to get some of these things!
It smells so good!
Put those over there, yeah?
I can't wait!
You're not scared of a
little alcohol, are you?
No, I just want to pace myself.
Okay, so the worst MMO
I ever played was...
this one from the U .S.
called Insect Site.
Uh, that one's bad. Really?
Why don't you like it?
Bugs everywhere!
If it were just the monsters, no problem!
But you gotta play as a bug!
I had to play as a bipedal ant, so
I guess I didn't have it too bad.
But you should have seen her.
No!
Please don't say anything!
She was a giant caterpillar!
Spitting silk like whoo!
That's awesome.
Sounds like you got to travel to
some really cool places together.
How about you?
I mean, you come off like you've
been playing VR Miss forever. Do I?
Well, I play this one a lot.
I can't tell you how many hours it took
to get the money to buy this cabin.
Worth it.
You know, when you said this place
was cozy, you weren't kidding.
It's got this really cool old-timey vibe.
Yes, it does.
It's so peaceful, I
could sit here all day.
What's wrong, Sune?
I'm so sorry, but I just remembered
when we asked you to help.
We said we'd give you whatever
the boss dropped in return.
It was money though, and we spent a lot
of it on food and drink for our party.
What have we done?
Crap!
Now we don't have anything to give you!
No, it's okay.
How about a favor instead?
Favor?
Honestly, I'm a little
sad the quest is over.
I want to get to know you better, Yuki.
There are so many things
I want to ask you.
Asuna, sometimes you gotta
fight to get your point across.
Yuki, would you let me
join this sleeping night?
Asuna, i wish you could, but it's
like this is a temporary thing for us.
And like, come spring
we'll be splitting up.
And after that, i doubt any of
us will be diving much anymore?
I know, but can I join until then?
I want us to be friends
I want to be friends with all of you.
There's still enough time
for that, isn't there?
I...
I'm sorry, Asuna.
You can't. Sorry.
Not at all.
It's fine.
I shouldn't have put you on
the spot like that, Yuki.
I'm sorry.
Um, Asuna...
I don't...
you see, we...
No, really.
You don't have to be.
Sorry I was so pushy.
Anyway, come on.
Let's go check it out.
What?
The reason we beat the boss, remember?
You know, the monument
in the Black Iron Palace.
I'm sure it's been updated
by now. Yeah, guys. Let's go.
Oh, know what we should do?
We should take our picture with it.
Good idea. Best one yet. Oh, my gosh.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
Hey, let's go.
All right, let's do it.
Let's get out of here.
I can't wait.
There it is!
Hey, wait for me! Look!
Look.
Up there.
There we are.
We got our names on it.
Hey, guys!
Let's take that picture!
Come on, Yuki. Big smile.
There it is. You did it.
Yeah, I finally did. How's this?
There you go again, Yuki.
What?
You called me sis just now. That's what.
And in the boss room, too.
It's fine.
It makes me happy.
What's wrong?
Asuna, I...
I...
Yuki!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Next time, the end of the journey